D E B J O H N S O N

PRODUCT DESIGNER

SKILLS

UX/UI DESIGN

USER RESEARCH

USER TESTING

PROTOTYPING

HTML/CSS

TOOLS

SKETCH

AFFINITY DESIGNER

INVISION

ABOUT

I'm a self-taught product designer and front-end developer (HTML/CSS). I was part of the founding team of a startup and wore many hats before discovering my passion for product design. My primary interests lie in user experience, user research, prototyping, and user testing.

EXPERIENCE

Neon Labs

PRODUCT DESIGNER

SAN FRANCISCO, CA FEB. 2013 - APRIL 2016

- Established company's design process and best practices
- Led user research to validate product directions; explored UX/UI concepts with rapid prototyping and user testing
- Designed analytics dashboard to display A/B testing data; worked with engineers to implement solution
- Designed internal tool to search through thousands of images generated by product

Neon Labs

DATA SCIENTIST

SAN FRANCISCO, CA FEB. 2012 - FEB 2013

- Member of founding team; played crucial role in crafting early product vision and building MVPs
- Helped define company culture, vision, and values
- Worked closely with CEO to design pitch decks that helped raise over \$8M in venture funding

Carnegie Mellon University

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

PITTSBURGH, PA SEP. 2010 - FEB 2012

 Helped find commercial application for neuroscience research on how the brain perceives visual images, which led to the founding of Neon Labs

EDUCATION

Dartmouth College

B.A. Psychology, Music

deb@debjohnson.design

603-738-0035

http://debjohnson.design

HANOVER, NH 2006 - 2010